[
  {
    "question": "Which of the following terms BEST describes a silhouette portrait?",
    "a": "interactive",
    "b": "quick",
    "c": "massive",
    "d": "complex",
    "e": "expensive",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Silhouettes were also referred to as",
    "a": "\"dark outlines\"",
    "b": "“likenesses”",
    "c": "\"shadow sketches\"",
    "d": "“shadow portraits”",
    "e": "“impressions\"",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "A physiognotrace would",
    "a": "increase the size of a silhouette",
    "b": "quicken a silhouette",
    "c": "produce multiple copies of a silhouette",
    "d": "add color to a silhouette",
    "e": "add detail to a silhouette",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following engravers invented the physiognotrace?",
    "a": "Gilles-Louis Chrétien",
    "b": "Paul Angiers",
    "c": "Jacopo de' Barbari",
    "d": "Jacques Callot",
    "e": "Albrecht Dürer",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following cities contained the first natural history museum in America?",
    "a": "Philadelphia",
    "b": "Boston",
    "c": "Newport",
    "d": "New York City",
    "e": "Charleston",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Charles Wilson Peale’s museum included all of the following items EXCEPT",
    "a": "science models",
    "b": "portraits of American leaders",
    "c": "wax figures",
    "d": "Mayan mummies",
    "e": "taxidermied birds",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following inventors inspired Charles Wilson Peale’s physiognotrace?",
    "a": "John Hawkins",
    "b": "John Bardeen",
    "c": "Thomas Edison",
    "d": "James Naismith",
    "e": "Eli Whitney",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following machines traces the outline of a sitter’s silhouette in a physiognotrace?",
    "a": "stereoscope",
    "b": "pantograph",
    "c": "oscillograph",
    "d": "daguerreotype",
    "e": "zoopraxiscope",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Followers of phrenology claimed that a person's face revealed their",
    "a": "intelligence",
    "b": "illnesses",
    "c": "character",
    "d": "social status",
    "e": "destiny",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the early nineteenth century, phrenologists asserted that criminals had all of the following characteristics EXCEPT",
    "a": "hawk-like noses",
    "b": "sloping foreheads",
    "c": "fox-like ears",
    "d": "hard shift eyes",
    "e": "low foreheads",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "To which group of people did silhouettes especially appeal?",
    "a": "the middle class",
    "b": "African Americans",
    "c": "white Americans",
    "d": "the wealthy",
    "e": "the poor",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Early American society gave silhouettes the label of",
    "a": "\"accurate image\"",
    "b": "\"honest depiction\"",
    "c": "\"clear likeness\"",
    "d": "\"true representation”",
    "e": "\"the American portrait\"",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Silhouettes reflected the republican value of",
    "a": "rugged individualism",
    "b": "charity",
    "c": "hard work",
    "d": "modesty",
    "e": "freedom",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Silhouettes laid the groundwork for the success of",
    "a": "oil portraiture",
    "b": "photography",
    "c": "minimalism",
    "d": "performance art",
    "e": "acrylics",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following organizations currently holds the portrait of Moses Williams?",
    "a": "Simmons University Library",
    "b": "the Rosenbach organization",
    "c": "the Library Company of Philadelphia",
    "d": "the Library of Congress",
    "e": "the Barnes Foundation",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following technologies did NOT have a significant effect on the nineteenth century?",
    "a": "railroad",
    "b": "radio",
    "c": "steamboat",
    "d": "cotton gin",
    "e": "telegraph",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following art styles emerged in the same year as Eadward Muybridge’s photographic experiments?",
    "a": "Impressionism",
    "b": "Minimalism",
    "c": "Abstractionism",
    "d": "Naturalism",
    "e": "Realism",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "In his photographic experiments, Eadweard Muybridge used technological advancements in",
    "a": "photo distance",
    "b": "shutter speed",
    "c": "camera mobility",
    "d": "camera storage",
    "e": "lens clarity",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "The work of Eadweard Muybridge led to the creation of",
    "a": "aerial photography",
    "b": "scientific photography",
    "c": "instantaneous photography",
    "d": "digital photography",
    "e": "landscape photography",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following questions did Leland Stanford hope to answer?",
    "a": "What is the most efficient way for a horse to gallop?",
    "b": "How high do horses come off the ground when they gallop?",
    "c": "Do horses fully extend their legs when they gallop?",
    "d": "Do all horses gallop in the same way?",
    "e": "Is there a moment in a horse’s gallop where all four hooves left the ground at the same time?",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "In order to capture The Horse in Motion, Eadweard Muybridge used",
    "a": "14 cameras",
    "b": "13 cameras",
    "c": "11 cameras",
    "d": "15 cameras",
    "e": "12 cameras",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "After his work with Leland Stanford, Muybridge worked at",
    "a": "the Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "b": "the University of Texas at Austin",
    "c": "the University of Pennsylvania",
    "d": "Harvard University",
    "e": "the University of California, Los Angeles",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following scenes would NOT have appeared in Eadweard Muybridge's Animal Locomotion?",
    "a": "a bird sleeping",
    "b": "a lion pacing",
    "c": "a dog trotting",
    "d": "a man boxing",
    "e": "a woman making a bed",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Eadweard Muybridge produced Animal Locomotion alongside the painter",
    "a": "John Singer Sargent",
    "b": "Thomas Eakins",
    "c": "Frederic Remington",
    "d": "Winslow Homer",
    "e": "Charles Dana Gibson",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rebecca Solnit explained the fixation with Muybridge's The Horse In Motion by drawing connections between changing perceptions of movement and",
    "a": "film",
    "b": "photography",
    "c": "speed",
    "d": "time",
    "e": "technology",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Critics of Eadweard Muybridge's The Horse In Motion claimed that it was",
    "a": "fake",
    "b": "circumstantial",
    "c": "incorrect",
    "d": "too short",
    "e": "inconclusive",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Muybridge used his zoopraxiscope primarily to",
    "a": "win a scientific competition",
    "b": "conduct research",
    "c": "create films",
    "d": "enhance his lectures",
    "e": "write his book",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "The zoopraxiscope is a device that",
    "a": "breaks down an image into multiple parts",
    "b": "creates the illusion of a moving picture",
    "c": "layers multiple images onto one another",
    "d": "slowly scrolls through images",
    "e": "displays an image on a large screen",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "The zoopraxiscope became an important precursor to modern",
    "a": "cinema",
    "b": "photography",
    "c": "research",
    "d": "performance art",
    "e": "portraiture",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Eadweard Muybridge's zoopraxiscope garnered attention at the",
    "a": "1895 Cotton States and International Exhibition",
    "b": "1895 Exhibition of Art and Industry",
    "c": "1889 Exposition Universelle",
    "d": "1892 Exposition of the Three Americas",
    "e": "1893 World's Columbian Exposition",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  }
]

